

JAKE BROKAW

ABOUT ME

Hey there. I'm a web designer and front-end developer. My wife, our two cats, and I are currently in the process of moving to Portland, Oregon, which will be the fourth city in the past five years where we have lived. Besides designing and coding websites, I enjoy reading books about philosophy, hiking, and drinking a good cup of coffee or tea.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TOLEDO

B.B.A. Information Systems 2008 - 2012

CONTACT



jacobrokaw.com



@jacobrokaw



@iacobrokaw



jacobrokaw@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

Formstack // Feb. 2015 - Present

I work remotely on the marketing design team. Some of my duties include: designing & building responsive web pages, optimizing our site's speed & performance, and designing marketing materials (i.e. ads, emails, graphics, etc.). Our small team recently created a brand new design system and migrated our entire codebase over to said system.

O DEVELOPER, IT APPLICATIONS

Nationwide Insurance // Feb. 2013 - Feb. 2015

I was the only front-end developer on a team that handled one of Nationwide Insurance's financial applications. I also helped out other teams when they were updating their apps to be fully responsive.

WEB SYSTEMS ASSOCIATE

Global Media Outreach // Jun. 2012 - Feb. 2013

I was one of six students to recieve what started out as an internship out in San José, CA. I worked with the development team to create and update websites. When the internship ended, I was offered a part-time remote position and worked as their Web Systems Associate.

SKILLS & SOFTWARE

✓ Responsive Design

✓ HTML

✓ Graphic Design

✓ CSS

✓ Design Systems

✓ SASS

✓ JavaScript

✓ PHP











